Guide to the John Eugene Unterecker Papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series VIII: Correspondence files
  - Coe, David
  - Coffee, Ricaldo
  - Cohen, Alan
  - Cohen, Lance
  - Cohen, Mort
  - Colburn, Jerry Lee
  - College English
  - Collier, Sandra
  - Collioure
  - Colorado Quarterly
  - Colum, Padraic
  - Columbia Forum
  - Columbia Noon readings
  - Columbia Poetry contests
  - Columbia University
  - Columbia University Address list
  - Columbia University Class lists
  - Columbia University Committee on graduate instruction
  - Columbia University Dissertations
  - Columbia University Press
  - Columbia Writers
  - Commentary
  - Conarroe, Joel (Box 10)
  - Congdon, Kirby
  - Connally, James
  - Conner, Lester
  - Conover, Roger -- editor, writer
  - Conrad, Cynthia
  - Contact
  - Contempora
  - Contemporary Authors
  - Contemporary Authors
  - Contemporary Literature
  - Cook, Christina
  - Cook, Reginald
  - Cooke, Ethelwyn
  - Cooper, Earl
  - Cooper, Gary
  - Cooper, Michael
  - Copeland, Keith
  - Corbin, John
  - Cordier, Andrew
  - Core, George
  - Cornell, Louis
  - Corrigan, Frank
  - Costazo, Gerald
  - Cotrell, Georgia
  - Courage, Alice (Box 11)
  - Covatta, Tony
  - Cox, Mrs. Howard
  - Cox, James
  - J.U. Hart Crane Walk
  - Crane, Theodore R.
  - Crawford, David
  - Crawford, John
  - Crazy Horse
  - Creed, Walter
  - Crile, Susan
  - Critical Quarterly
  - Crowell, Thomas Y. -- publishers
  - Cuala Press
  - Cuddihy, Michael
  - Cullinan, John -- poet
  - Cummington Community of the Arts
  - Curtis, C. Michael
  - Curtis, Sam
  - Curtis, Sue
  - Dacey, Phil
  - Dalhousie Review
  - Dalton, Elizabeth
  - Dameron, Chip
  - Damon, Phil Dance -- modern dance programs
  - Daragon, Monique
  - Dasenbrock, Reedway
  - Davaran, Ardavan
  - Davie, Donald -- critic
  - Davis, Berenice
  - Davis, Kenneth
  - Davis, Roderick
  - Dawson, Carl
  - Dawson, Hugh
  - Day, A. Grove
  - Dayton, David
  - December
  - Dekalb Literary Arts Journal
  - Delaney, Paul
  - Delius, Jean
  - Demarco, Nicholas
  - Deming, Barbara
  - Deninger, Rose
  - Denney, Renee
  - Denver Quarterly
  - Denzer, Mark
  - De Rodrigues, Electa Arenal
  - Despain, Larene (Box 12)
  - Dettling, Mary Elizabeth
  - Deutsch, Babette -- poet
  - Develschow, Andrew
  - Devine, Lawrence
  - Dewitt, E.
  - Dickerson, George
  - Dickinson, Richard
  - Dieffie
  - Diggory, Terry
  - Diner, Steven
  - DiPalma, Ray - poet
  - Dobie, Mary
  - Dodson, Dan
  - Dolmen Press
  - Donadio, Stephen
  - Donaldson, Virginia
  - Donkor, Freeman
  - Donno, Elizabeth
  - Doones Magazine
  - Doran, Len
  - Dotterer, Ron
  - Doubleday
  - Doulis, Thomas
  - Dowling, Dean
  - Drew, Bob
  - Drew, Fraser
  - Drexel, John -- poet
  - Drinkwater, Cathy
  - Driscoll, Leon
  - Driver, Beverly
  - Driver, Tom
  - Druker, Roman
  - Dublin Magazine
  - Du Bois, William
  - Duffett, Diane
  - Duke University
  - Dumarin, Adele -- poet
  - Dumbrowsky, Paul
  - Duncan, Harry
  - Dunleavy, Janet
  - Dunlop, Barbara
  - Dunning, Becky
  - Dupee, Fred
  - Du Plessis, Rachel
  - Dyer, Mrs. Walter
  - East-West Conference (Box 13)
  - Economou, George
  - Edel, Leon
  - Edelstein, Arnie
  - Eden, Carl
  - Educational Testing Service
  - Edwards, Olivier
  - Egan, Michael
  - Ehrenpreis, Irvin -- critic
  - Eichenberger, V.F.
  - Eichrodt, John
  - Elbert, George A.
  - Eliot, T.S.
  - Elliot, Leslie
  - Elliot, Maurice
  - Ellman, Richard
  - Elmslie, Kenward
  - Encounter
  - Encyclopedia Americana -- miscellaneous
  - Encyclopedia Americana - 1960
  - Encyclopedia Americana - 1961
  - Encyclopedia Americana -- 1962
  - Encyclopedia Americana - 1963
  - Encyclopedia, Collier's
  - Encyclopedia, Italian
  - Encyclopedia, Oxford Junior
  - Engels, John
  - England -- photos (Box 14)
  - English Comp. Material
  - English Fiction in Translation
  - English -- general material
  - English Language News
  - Epoch
  - Epstein, David -- poet
  - Erickson, Errol
  - Eshelman, Eve
  - Eskey, David
  - Estrin, Herman
  - Evans, Dilys
  - Evans, Lawrence
  - Evans, Lorna
  - Evans, Ruth
  - Evarts, Prescott
  - Evergreen Review
  - Eyeler, Audrey
  - Fairey, Wendy
  - Fallon, Doug
  - Falvey, Kathleen
  - Farmer, David
  - Farrar, Straus, & Giroux
  - Fedigan, Dorothy
  - Fein, Carol
  - Feinberg, Sid
  - Feld, Bernard
  - Feldman, Leonard
  - Felix, Tanya
  - Felton, Kristi
  - Feltzer, Mary Ann
  - Feroz, Ahmed-Ud-Din
  - Ferrante, Joan
  - Ferreira, Russell
  - Ferris, Gertrude
  - Fessenden, Anne
  - Field Magazine
  - Field, Edward
  - Fink, Marta
  - Finneran, Richard
  - Fireman, Judy
  - Fisher, Lucy
  - Fitzpatrick, Annie
  - Flaccus, Karl
  - Flahtery, E.A.
  - Flannery, James -- Yeats critic
  - Fleece, Larry
  - Fleisher, Jack
  - Fletcher, (Professor)
  - Flin, Carol
  - Flinders University of South Australia
  - Flonder, Polly
  - Focus (Midwest)
  - Forni, Francesca
  - Forum (Columbia)
  - Forum (Houston)
  - Foster, Elaine
  - Foster, Elizabeth
  - Foster, Lee
  - Foster, Nelson
  - Foster, Richard
  - Foster, Susan
  - Fox, Siv Cedering
  - Fraenkel, George (Box 15)
  - Frame, Janet
  - Franke
  - Franzblau, Muriel
  - Fratelli Fabbri Editori
  - Frayne, John P.
  - Fredericks, Kayo
  - Fredman, Alice
  - Freedman, Morris
  - Freedman, Nadezhda
  - Freeman, Leslie
  - Freibert, Mark
  - Freitas, Roslyn
  - Fryer, Dr. Grattan -- Hibernian scholar
  - Frick, Richard
  - Firebert, Stuart -- poet, translator, editor
  - Friedman, Alan
  - Friedman, Jack
  - Friedson, Anthony
  - Friend, Albert
  - Firends of the Earth
  - Friends of the Library of Hawaii
  - Frierson, Pamela
  - Frierson, Wright
  - Fritch, Robert
  - Fruit
  - Frumkin, Gene -- poet
  - Fry, William
  - Frye, Burton
  - Fuchs, Miriam
  - Fujimoto, Wanda
  - Fujimura, Thomas
  - Fulbright Award
  - Fulton, Len
  - Fussell, Charles
  - Gable, Cathy
  - Galassi, John
  - Galin, Saul
  - Gallia, Pat
  - Galpin, Alfred
  - Galvin, John
  - Garbisch, Martha
  - Gardiner, Thomas J.
  - Gardner, Ann
  - Gardner, Isabella (Box 16)
  - Gardner, Shan
  - Garraty, John A.
  - Garrett, Caroline
  - Gasparinni, Len
  - Gassner, John
  - Gatenby, Greg
  - Gattuso, Josephine
  - Gavin, David
  - Gay, Harriet
  - Gay, Laurence
  - Gazdick, Betty
  - Gearen, Barbara
  - Geil, William
  - Georgia Review
  - Gerber, Dan
  - Gerber, Judith
  - Gere, David
  - Germano, Bill
  - Gershel, Alice
  - Gershel, Jennie
  - Gershon, Karen
  - Gialis, John
  - Gibbons, Emma
  - Gifford, Bill
  - Gilbert, El
  - Gilbert, Peter
  - Gilborn, Alice
  - Gildzen, Alex
  - Giles, Richard
  - Gill, Lorena
  - Gilmore, Haydn
  - Gilmour, Doug
  - Gilt Edge
  - Gingerich, Susan
  - Ginsberg, Allen
  - Gioseffi, Daniela
  - Glass, Mr. Martin
  - Gluck, Barbara
  - Gochros, Harvey (Box 17)
  - Goebel, Lee
  - Gold, Mrs. Herbert
  - Gold, Michael
  - Goldberg, Miriam
  - Goldblatt, Emily
  - Goldblatt, Sigmund
  - Goldman, Jerry and Irene
  - Goldman, Martin
  - Goldsberry, Steven
  - Goldstein, Sylvia
  - Gonzales, Laurence
  - Goodman, jeanne
  - Gordon, Herbert
  - Gott, Lisa
  - Grable, Lindy
  - Graham, David -- poet
  - Graham, Elliot
  - Graham, Judy
  - Gratton, Francis
  - Gray, Jim
  - Gray, Mary F.
  - Greece
  - Green, Bob
  - Green, Galen
  - Greet, Cabell
  - Gregory, Dorothy
  - Gregory, Hilda
  - Griffith, E.V.
  - Groden, S.Q.
  - Gronachan, Cathy
  - Gronachan, James and Frances
  - Gronau, Kurt
  - Gross, Sandra
  - Grove Press
  - Gruenstein, Diane
  - Guang, Yang
  - Guggenheim Foundation
  - Gurko, Leo
  - Gussin, Lenore
  - Gustaitis, Joe
  - Guy, Eugene Marie
  - Gwiazda, Ron
  - Hable, Herb
  - Hagen, Fred
  - Hagen, Sara
  - Hagstrom, Jack
  - Haleakala Poetry Journal
  - Hall, Wade (Box 18)
  - Hallmark Poetry Contest
  - Halper, Nathan
  - Halpern, Dan -- editor, poet
  - Halpern, Max
  - Halpert, Suzanna
  - Halzer, C.
  - Hamasaki, Richard
  - Hamblin, John
  - Hammond, Anne
  - Hammond, Mac
  - Hanley, Mary
  - Hannah, Dennis
  - Hanning, Robert
  - Hanson, Catherine
  - Hanson, Donald
  - Hanson, Polly
  - Hara, Marie
  - Harada, Jane
  - Hardaway, Nancine
  - Harding, Gene
  - Harley, Helen
  - Harmon, Maurice
  - Harnack, Curt
  - Harper and Row
  - Harper, George
  - Harper, Michael -- poet
  - Harper's Bazaar
  - Harper's Magazine
  - Harrel, Margaret
  - Harrex, Syd -- writer
  - Harris, Marguerite
  - Harstead, Wallace
  - Hartman, Lee
  - Hartung, George W.
  - Hartwell, David
  - Haruka, Setsuko O' Hara
  - Harvard University Press
  - Harvey, David
  - Harwood, Betty
  - Haskell, Phyllis
  - Haskins, Norka
  - Hass, Robert -- poet
  - Hawaii Dance Theatre, Ltd.
  - HLAC
  - Hawaii Literary Review (Box 19)
  - Hawaii Review
  - Hawaii, University of
  - Haydn, Hiram
  - Hayes, Robert and Eunice
  - Hayner, Isabelle
  - Hazen, Allan
  - Head, Gwen
  - Heady, Virginia
  - Healey, Arthur
  - Healy, James A.
  - Hearse
  - Hecht, Roger
  - Hedstrom, Lois and Monica
  - Heenan, David
  - Heffner, Mike
  - Heilbrun, Carolyn
  - Heine, Elizabeth
  - Held, Arnold
  - Heller, Michael
  - Helms, Alan
  - Helstoski, Henry
  - Hemley, Cecil
  - Hendin, Josephine (Gattuso)
  - Henry, Terry
  - Herald Tribune book review
  - Herendeen, Warren
  - Heringman, Bernard
  - Herrmann (Box 20)
  - Herzfeld, Herb
  - Hess, Shirley
  - Heuston, Edward
  - Hewitt, Geof
  - Hicks, Dottle
  - Hicks, John
  - Higdon, Alexis
  - Higgins, Judith
  - Highwood Hills Campaign
  - Hildebrand, Mike
  - Hilgers, Tom
  - Hill and Wang
  - Hill, John
  - Hill, Kathy
  - Hillman, Sid
  - Hine, Daryl
  - Hirschberg, Stuart
  - History of Ideas newsletter
  - Hitchcock, George
  - Hlyne, Ma Tin and Pe
  - Hochman, Sandra
  - Hoff, Vivian
  - Hoffman, Dan
  - Hoffman, Jill
  - Hofrichter, Sue
  - Holland, Barbara
  - Holland, P.J.
  - Holmes, Elizabeth
  - Holroyd, Michael -- biographer
  - Holt, Rinehart & Winston
  - Holt, John Dominus
  - Holzer, Charlotte
  - Honma, Wade
  - Honolulu City Ballet
  - Hood, Sharon
  - Hope-McCarthy, Eleanor
  - Hormann, Nicholas
  - Horne, Janet S.
  - Horowitz, Ruth G.
  - Horsting, Eric
  - Horton, Sarah
  - Horvath, Adam
  - Hoskins, H.W.
  - Houghton Mifflin Anthology
  - Hovde, Carl (Box 21)
  - Howard, Quentin
  - Howard, Richard
  - Howden, Michael
  - Howe, Lois
  - Howe, Marguerite
  - Huberman, Edward
  - Huddle, David -- poet
  - Hudson Review
  - Hudson River Anthology
  - Huffman, Cliff
  - Hugo, Richard
  - Hulbert, Debra
  - Hulme, Keri
  - Hunt, Alice
  - Hunter, Jerome
  - Huntsberry, William
  - Hurwitz, Harold
  - Hutchins, Patricia
  - Hyman, Virginia
  - Hynes, Samuel
  - Ibrahim, A. Ghafar
  - Illinois - University of Illinois Press
  - Imada, David
  - Imura, Kimie
  - Indiana University Press
  - Inez, Colette
  - Ingram, Sukey
  - Ino, Anne
  - Inouye, Daniel - senator of Hawaii
  - Institute of All Nations
  - Interstate
  - Invitation to Learning
  - Irons, Rosemary
  - Ironwood
  - Irwin, Art
  - Isosaki, Robin
  - Ito, Ann
  - Ito, Elden
  - Ivens, Michael
  - Jwasa, Warren
  - Izubachi, Hiro
  - Jackel, Karen
  - Jackson, Ralph H.
  - Jaffee, Ellen Sue
  - Jakobovits, Leon
  - Jam-To-Day
  - Jantz, Harold
  - Jantz, Rudy
  - Jarrett, Emmett
  - Jeffares, A. Norman
  - Jellema, Roderick
  - Jemie, Onwuchekwa
  - Jenkins, Lee
  - Jenks, Amy
  - Jennison, Peter
  - Jerome, Judson -- poet
  - Jewel, Michael
  - Jivan
  - Johnson, B.S.
  - Johnson, Coulton -- critic
  - Johnson, Don
  - Johnson, Edgar
  - Johnson, Fred
  - Johnson, Jim
  - Johnson, Keith
  - Johnson, Loretta
  - Johnson, Mark
  - Johnston, Jane
  - Jones, Betty
  - Jones, Diana
  - Jones, Gregory
  - Jordon, Elena
  - Josephson, Elissa
  - Jost, E.J.
  - Journal of English and Germanic Philology
  - Judd, William
  - Judson, John
  - Kagehird, Phyllis
  - Kahlert, Shirley
  - Kamins, Shirley
  - Kanemitsu, Daniel
  - Kantor, Jonathan
  - Kapa
  - Karchmer, Gordon
  - Karchmer, Sylvan
  - Kardon, Annette
  - Karkas, Carmen
  - Karl, Fred
  - Jasatkina, Ljudnila -- Russian poet
  - Kasper, Joseph
  - Katz, Leslie
  - Kau, Joe
  - Kauai
  - Kaufman, Shirley
  - Kaufmann, Carolyn
  - Kauka
  - Kauraka, kauraku -- poet
  - Keane, Patrick
  - Keegan, Frank
  - Keener, Fredrick
  - Keener, Grant
  - Kelley, John
  - Kemble, Janet
  - Kendall, Donald
  - Kendrick, John
  - Keneally, Tom
  - Kennedy, Eileen
  - Kennedy, Signie
  - Kennelly, Brandon -- Irish poet
  - Kenner, Hugh -- critic
  - Kenney, Rick -- poet
  - Kentucky Poetry Review
  - Kenyon Review
  - Kersnowski, Frank L.
  - Kessler, Milton (Box 23)
  - Key, Ronald
  - Kherdian, David
  - Kicknosway, Faye
  - Kidder, Rusworth
  - Kiell, Norman
  - Kiesel, Stanley
  - Kilbourne, Benji
  - Kim, Elaine
  - Kim, Glen
  - Kim, Jama
  - Kimata, Glenn
  - Kindley, Jeff
  - King, Susan M.
  - Kingsley, Gordon
  - Kingston, Maxine Hong -- novelist
  - Kinnell, Galway
  - Kinoian, Vartkis
  - Kinoshita, Eleanor
  - Kinzer, Illona
  - Kirby-Smith, Tom-Noel
  - Kirk, Jo
  - Kirkpatrick, Dan
  - Kirsh, Susan
  - Kirstein, Lincoln
  - Kissick, Gary -- poet
  - Kitchen, Judith
  - Kleiner, Elaine
  - Kleinjans, Everett
  - Klinger, Ramona
  - Kluzak, Zdenek
  - Knapp, Elise
  - Knight, Alan Stuart
  - Knight, Etheridge
  - Knopf, Inc.
  - Knox, George
  - Knox, Gregory
  - Koban, Charles
  - Kobayashi, Mangi
  - Koch, Jayne
  - Koch, Kenneth
  - Kodama, Kathy
  - Koergater, L.W.
  - Koki, Srthur
  - Kolesar, Peter and Nicolle
  - Komesu, Okifumi
  - Komi, Susan
  - Kook, Young Suh (Box 24)
  - Korn, Alfons
  - Kostalanetz, Richard
  - Kourte, Joanne
  - Kowal, Dennis
  - Krakauer
  - Kramer, Maurice
  - Kraus, matt
  - Kraus, Susan
  - Kresge, Lisa
  - Krieger, Murray
  - Kroeber, Karl
  - Krogfus, Miles E.
  - Kroll, Jeri L.
  - Krupat, Arnold
  - Krupper, Joseph
  - Kubu, Leonard
  - Kuczkowski, Dick
  - Kuenstler, Frank
  - Kumai, Marline
  - Kuribayashi, Laurie
  - Kusonoki, Tomoki Paul
  - Kuzma, Greg
  - Labaton, Arnold
  - Lagory, Michael
  - Lagoudis, Jane
  - LaGuardia, Eric
  - Lakehomen, Leona
  - Lan, Gordon
  - Landen, Melrick
  - Landen, Phaenon(Noni)
  - Lander, David
  - Landergan, Mary
  - Landis, James
  - Lane, Gary
  - Langer, Suzanne
  - Langford, Kathy
  - Lanier, Kay
  - Lanning, George
  - Lanziolati, Rose and Jack
  - Lardos, Konstantinos
  - Lareau, Eugene A.
  - La Riviere, Gladys
  - Larkin, Emmet
  - Larned, Gay
  - Larsen, Erling
  - Larson, Dick
  - Lask, Tom
  - Latch, Daniel
  - Lau, Raymond
  - Lavender, Andrew
  - Layton, Dave
  - Lea, Sydney
  - Leach, Mary Lee
  - Leach, Wilford
  - Leary, Lewis
  - Leborg, Michael
  - Lechay, Jo
  - Lee, Donald W.
  - Lee, Peter H.
  - Lehman, David
  - Leib, Amos
  - Leibowitz, Herbert
  - Leigh, David
  - Leighton, John
  - Leiman, Arnold
  - Lennon, Florence Becker
  - Lentz, Lynn
  - Leonard, George J.
  - Leonards, Helen Hope
  - Lepage, Joseph
  - Lessa, Rich
  - Leton, Renee
  - Leverenz, David
  - Leverenz, Michael
  - Levin, Barbara
  - Levine, Al
  - Levitin, Alexis
  - Levy, Al
  - Levy, William
  - Lewis, James
  - Lewis, Dick (Richard Allen)
  - Lewis, May
  - Lewis, Stanley
  - Lewis, Tom
  - Ley, Lindy
  - Lieberman, Jerri
  - Lieberman, Larry
  - Lifshin, Lyn
  - Light Year
  - Lillabullero
  - Lindberg, Stanley
  - Lindell, Doe
  - Lindquist, Mark
  - Lindsley, M.F.
  - Linett, Lee
  - Links Books
  - Linney, Romulus
  - Lino, Tanya
  - Linthicum, John
  - Literary Review
  - Little Magazine
  - Litz, Walton
  - Locke, Duane
  - Locke, Lawrence
  - Lockwood, lee
  - Lockwood Memorial Library
  - Loftis, Norman
  - Logan, Cynthia
  - Logan, John
  - Lohf, Kenneth
  - Lombardi, Tom
  - London, Michael
  - Long, David
  - Long, JIm
  - Long, Robert
  - Look, Lin (Box 26)
  - LouisianaUniversity State Press
  - Lourdes, Claudia
  - Lucas, Cora
  - Lucas, Frankie
  - Luden, Fritz
  - Ludwig, R. -- Pegasus Press
  - Lundeen, Min
  - Lutcher, Bob and Laura
  - Lux, Thomas
  - Lynch, Mary Ann
  - Lyons, Jeff
  - Lytle, Andrew
  - McAleer, Mary
  - McAlindon, T.
  - McCartan, Patrick
  - McCarthy, Carol
  - McClelland, Lee
  - McCorry, Eileen
  - McCredie, Kathi
  - McCuen, James
  - McCurdy, Ronald
  - McCutcheon, Elizabeth
  - McDiarmid, Lucy -- critic
  - Mcdonald, Cynthia -- poet
  - Macdonald, Roderic
  - McDonough, George
  - McDowell, Carol
  - McElhane, Patricia
  - McElwee, Thomas
  - McGill, Anne
  - McGill, William
  - McGonagill, Gerry
  - MacGowran, Jack and Gloria
  - McGrath, Tom
  - McGraw-Hill
  - McGrory, Kathleen
  - McHenry, Bob
  - McKee, Mel
  - Lackenzie, James
  - McKinney, Diana
  - Macknight
  - McLaughlin, Ann
  - Macmillan, Ian
  - Macmillan Company
  - Macnamara, Gael
  - Macnamera, Richard
  - MacNeven, Ian (Box 27)
  - McNurney, Ruth
  - McPherson, Michael
  - McQuiggan, John
  - MacShane, Frank -- biographer
  - McVeigh, Paul
  - McVicar, James
  - Machell, Richard
  - Machett, William
  - Mack, Maynard -- critic
  - Macy, Miko
  - Magid, Nora
  - Mahon, D.W.
  - Mahon, Michael
  - Mahoney, Jack
  - Mahoney, Nengin
  - Makaris, Mary
  - Malagi
  - Malamud
  - Malamud, Janna
  - Malamud, Paul
  - Malin, Irving
  - Malkoat, Phil
  - Malkoff, Karl
  - Mallery, Kathleen
  - Maltby, Joseph
  - Malone, Emmett
  - Manabe, Jody
  - Mandel, Oscar -- poet
  - Manfield, Aaron
  - Manganaro, Mark
  - Maraldo, Bill (Box 28)
  - Marcus, Mort
  - Marder, Herbert
  - Margulies, Martin
  - Mark, Anna
  - Mark, Wendy
  - Marlatt, Daphne
  - Maroldo, W.J.
  - Marsano, Mark
  - Marsh, Erika
  - Marshall, Jerry
  - Martin, Augustine
  - Martin, Gus -- Irish scholar
  - Martin, James
  - Martin, Robert
  - Martinique -- misc.
  - Marum, Andrew
  - Marx, Anne
  - Mason, Richard G.
  - Massachusetts Review
  - Matchett, William H.
  - Matison, Barbara
  - Matranga, Joseph
  - Matsueda, Pat -- poet
  - Matsunaga, Brad
  - Matsunaga, Spark
  - Matthews, Aiden -- poet
  - Matthews, Jack
  - Matthews, Terry
  - Matthews, William
  - May, Wong
  - Mayer, Elaine
  - Mayer, Stephen
  - Mazzara, Jerome -- poet
  - Mazzeo, Joe
  - Mazzilla, Tony
  - Mehus, Donald
  - Meigs, Mary
  - Meisel, M.
  - Meiss, Millard
  - Meites, Louis
  - Mellott, Leland
  - Melton, Hollis
  - Menczkowski, Olava
  - Mendel, Doug
  - Menikoff, Barry
  - Mercier, Vivian
  - Merlan, Thomas
  - Merriman, Jim
  - Messing, Sara
  - Meyer, Catherine
  - Meyer, Melissa (Box 29)
  - Meyers, Jeffrey
  - Michel, Carole
  - Michelson, Peter
  - Michigan Quarterly Review
  - Mid-American Review
  - Middendorf, John
  - Middlebrook, Diane
  - Middleton, Linda
  - Mideast Quarterly
  - Milburg, Ruth
  - Milford, Nancy
  - Milicia, Joseph
  - Miller, Charles
  - Miller, Don
  - Miller, J. Hillis -- critic
  - Miller, Rand
  - Miller, Stuart
  - Millgate, Michael
  - Mills, Ralph J.
  - Minnesota Review
  - Mirollo, James
  - Miscellany
  - Miyahia, Sheryl
  - Miyamoto, Stanley
  - Miyasoto, Bill
  - Modell, Judith
  - Modern Age
  - Modern Drama
  - Modern Language Quarterly
  - Moers, Ellen -- critic
  - Moffett, Judith
  - Moffi, Larry
  - Molloy, Michael V.
  - Monblatt, Jean
  - Monmouth Theatre
  - Montney, Marv
  - Mooney, Jack
  - Moore, John
  - Moran, Kitty
  - Moraytes, John
  - Morgan, Barbara
  - Morgan, Ernest
  - Morgan, Fredrick
  - Morgan, Maud
  - Morioko, K.
  - Morris, Robert J.
  - Morris, Tayler
  - Morrison, Boone
  - Morrison, James
  - Morrison, Marsha
  - Morrow, Felix (Box 30)
  - Morse, J. Mitchell
  - Morton, Murray
  - Moss, Robert
  - Motooka, Joann
  - Mott, Michael
  - Mower, Nancy
  - Muller, Lisel
  - Mullaney, John
  - Mullen, Kathleen
  - Mullen, Richard F.
  - Muller, Freddy
  - Muller, Lucienne
  - Mullins, Kathleen
  - Mulvey, Christopher
  - Mundus Artium
  - Munford, Howard
  - Munro, John
  - Murayama, Lorraine
  - Murphy, Dan
  - Murphy, Richard
  - Musella, Bill
  - Myers, Robert
  - Naone, Dana
  - Nason, Richard
  - Nathan, Norman
  - Nathan, Wallace
  - Nation, The
  - National Book Committee -- biography 1974
  - National Endowment for the Arts
  - National Endowment for the Humanities
  - National Humanities Center
  - National Society of Arts and Letters
  - Nelson, Bill (Box 31)
  - Nelson, Howard
  - Nelson, Paul
  - Nelson, Peter
  - Nero, Bob
  - New England Review
  - New Jersey Association of Teachers of English
  - New Jersey Women's Club Poetry Contest
  - New Leader
  - New Letters
  - New Mexico Quarterly
  - New Orleans Review
  - NYC Ballet Program
  - New York Graphic Society
  - New York Quarterly
  - New York Times
  - New York University
  - New Yorker
  - Newport, Tuck
  - Newton, Ray
  - Nghiem, Aaron
  - Nichols, Douglas
  - Nicholson, Peter
  - Nickels, Kirby L.
  - Nicolson, Marjorie
  - Nimrod (Box 32)
  - Nimtz, Steven
  - Nitchie, George
  - Nitschke
  - Nizalowski, John
  - Nochimson, Linda
  - Noel, Gordon
  - Noll, Bink
  - Noonan, Gary
  - Noonday correspondence
  - Noone, P.
  - Norman, Howard
  - North, Charlie
  - Northwest Review
  - Norton, W.W. and Co.
  - Novicki, Chet
  - Nowlan, Kevin
  - Nyland, Nova
  - Nyyssonen, Paula
  - Oak, Kilsung
  - Oberlin Quarterly
  - O'Brian, Patrick
  - O'Brien, E.P.
  - O'Brien, Justin
  - O'Brien, Michael
  - Ochester, Ed
  - O'Connell, Daniel
  - O'Connor, Chris
  - Oda, Reiko
  - O'Dalaigh, Michael
  - O'Daly, Michael
  - O'Donnell, Mari-Louise
  - O'Donnell, William
  - O'Grady, Tom
  - O'Hara, James
  - Ohara, Setsuko
  - Ohio Review
  - Ohio University
  - Ohye, Edward
  - Oi, Judy (Box 33)
  - Okada, Sumie
  - Okimoto, Eric
  - Oksendahl, W.
  - Olaguer, Vlademar
  - Ollen, Jim
  - Olney, James -- critic
  - Olson, Charles
  - Ondaatje, Michael
  - Onopa, Bob
  - Orr, Gregory (3 folders, 2 envelopes)
  - Osaka, Sam
  - Oser, Fred
  - Oshima, S.
  - Osowski, E.J.
  - Ottaviano, Gioia
  - Owen, Guy
  - Ownby, Jim
  - Oxford University Press
  - Pacana, Nicholas (Box 34)
  - Pack, Robert
  - Packard, William
  - Page, Carol
  - Pahlaka, Bill
  - Palka, Bill
  - Palmer, John
  - Pang, Carolyn
  - Paoli, Dennis
  - Parini, Jay -- poet
  - Paris Review
  - Park, April
  - Parker, Linda
  - Parker, Richard
  - Parkinson, Thomas
  - Parris, Ed -- poet
  - Parris, Roger
  - Parson, J.
  - Parsons, Coleman
  - Partisan Review
  - Patrides, C.A.
  - Patterson, Cindy
  - Patterson, R.P.
  - Paul, Don
  - Paul, Sherman
  - Pawlovski, Bob
  - Payne, Basil
  - Payne, John
  - Peabody, R.
  - Pearce, Richard
  - Pearce, Roy H.
  - Pearlman, Daniel
  - Pedden, Alison
  - Pedlow, Reed
  - Peetz, Mike
  - Pemberton, V.
  - P.E.N.
  - P.E.N. American Centre
  - Pendragon
  - Peoples, Lynne
  - Pereras, Vic and Padma
  - Perira, Padma
  - Perkins, P.C.
  - Perrine, Lawrence
  - Petersen, Don
  - Peterson, M.
  - Peterson, Patrice
  - Petrosky, Tony
  - Petry, Ann
  - Phelps, Dean
  - Phelps, Wylie
  - Photography
  - Piculin, Karl (Box 35)
  - Pilgrim, Hal
  - Pike, Li
  - Pilcer, Sonia
  - Pinchin, Jane
  - Pinkosh, Paul
  - Pinzow, Danny
  - Pitts, Nanlee Haston
  - Plainsong
  - Plamondon, Terry
  - Plantz, Allen
  - Pochada, Elizabeth
  - Poetry
  - Poetry Hawaii
  - Poetry Ireland
  - Poetry Northwest
  - Poetry Now
  - Poetry Society of America
  - Poetry Today
  - Poets and Writers, Inc.
  - Poets-in-the-Schools
  - Poets of Living Hawaii
  - Polhemus, R. -- critic
  - Poli, Kenneth
  - Pollard, Jennie
  - Pollitt, Katha
  - Pondrom, Cyrena N.
  - Popa, Vasco
  - Porteous, Alexandra
  - Porteous, Peter
  - Porter, Ray
  - Portnow, Marjorie
  - Poulos, Dot and Chris
  - Potts, Diana
  - Poulin, A.I.
  - Poulso, Dorothy
  - Povich, Anita
  - Prairie Schooner
  - Prange, S.
  - Prentice-Hall, Inc.
  - Prichard, Walt (Box 36)
  - Princeton University Press
  - Prism
  - Proffitt, Edward
  - Programs played by B.(?)
  - Provincetown Experimental Theatre
  - Pruitt, Gladys
  - Pughe, Debbie
  - Putnam, Peter
  - Quagliano, Tony
  - Quarterly Review of Literature
  - Quesenbery, William D., Jr.
  - Quinn, Edward
  - Quinn, Sister Bernetta
  - Quintet Review
  - Quintoro, Janet Sturman
  - Raab, Lawrence
  - Rabinowitz, Rubin